<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" xmlns:itunesu="http://www.itunesu.com/feed" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>San Diego Real Estate Podcast with Carlos Gutierrez</title>
    <link>http://localhost:4000</link>
    <atom10:link xmlns:atom10="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="http://localhost:4000"/>
    <description>If you are looking to buy or sell a home, get all the information and the latest updates, tips, and tricks from Coldwell Banker - your professional San Diego Real Estate Agents.</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <managingEditor>Carlos Gutierrez</managingEditor>
    <lastBuildDate>2018-12-13 13:53:27 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    <media:copyright>Carlos Gutierrez</media:copyright>
    <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000/img/podcast.jpg"/>
    <media:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in San Diego, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</media:keywords>
    <media:category scheme="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd">Education</media:category>
    <itunes:owner>
      <itunes:email>Carlos@CarlosGSellSSanDiego.com</itunes:email>
      <itunes:name>Carlos Gutierrez</itunes:name>
    </itunes:owner>
    <itunes:author>Carlos Gutierrez</itunes:author>
    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
    <itunes:image href="http://localhost:4000/img/podcast.jpg"/>
    <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in San Diego, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
    <itunes:subtitle>Learn all the tips, tricks and more for buyers and sellers in the San Diego Area Real Estate Market</itunes:subtitle>
    <itunes:summary>If you are looking to buy or sell a home, get all the information and the latest updates, tips, and tricks from Coldwell Banker - your professional San Diego Real Estate Agents.</itunes:summary>
      <itunes:category text="Education"/>
    
      <item>
        <title>Don't Take Our Word for It: Hear Why Carlos Is Different From His Clients</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/dont-take-our-word-for-it-hear-why.html</link>
        
          <category>Testimonials</category>
        
        <author>Carlos Gutierrez</author>
        <pubDate>2017-07-25 12:21:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid>https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Carlos+Gutierrez/+Video/2017/July/San+Diego+Real+Estate+Agent-+Client+testimonials-+How+is+Carlos+different%253F.mp4</guid>
        <description>

Carlos Gutierrez has been serving clients in San Diego County since 2005. Here’s what just a few of those clients have to say.

As a full-time real estate agent, Carlos Gutierrez has earned the Chairman’s Circle Platinum award for his sales performance in 2013, ranking him among the top 1% of Coldwell Banker sales associates. But, the successes most important to Carlos are the ones that come not in the form of awards, but in the form of satisfied clients.

Since 2005, Carlos has been serving buyers, sellers, and investors throughout San Diego County—treating each and every transaction as if it were his very own.
 And his clients have noticed.

Diane Gaske is one such client. She’s known Carlos for 25 years—since meeting him at the elementary school she once worked at. Years later, when it came time for Diane to sell the home she had lived in for 27 years, she knew she would need the right person to help.

For her, and many others, Carlos is that person.

“THE SUCCESSES MOST IMPORTANT TO CARLOS ARE THE ONES THAT COME IN THE FORM OF SATISFIED CLIENTS.”

She recalls Carlos sending postcards to all of her neighbors and hosting multiple open houses—something she says ultimately paid off, since her house sold in less than two weeks.
 Another client, Matthew, first encountered Carlos when he helped Matthew’s father to sell the home he had been struggling to sell for months in just 15 days. The reason for Carlos’ success, according to Matthew, is that he listens to clients and creates unique, detailed plans according to their needs.

Something that stuck with Matthew, specifically, is when Carlos came to him with a 27-point presentation explaining what he was going to do to sell his house. Matthew emphasized to us that what Carlos does is different for every client—because every client is different.

Matthew says that, because of this, “He was able to do what he said he was going to do.” He also says that Carlos only “promises what he can deliver” and that “his communication is extraordinary.”

Other clients had praise for Carlos, as well. According to Jan and Mike Neil, “You are foremost and number one in his mind” while you are working with him.

All of these people are real clients who Carlos has gone above and beyond for. So, if you are thinking of working with him, remember them when making your decision. Diane, who has known him for 25 years, says she recommends Carlos “110%.”

If you have any other questions or would like more information, feel free to give us a call or send us an email. We look forward to hearing from you, soon.
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Carlos+Gutierrez/+Video/2017/July/San+Diego+Real+Estate+Agent-+Client+testimonials-+How+is+Carlos+different%253F.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Carlos+Gutierrez/+Video/2017/July/San+Diego+Real+Estate+Agent-+Client+testimonials-+How+is+Carlos+different%253F.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>

Carlos Gutierrez has been serving clients in San Diego County since 2005. Here’s what just a few of those clients have to say.

</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Carlos Gutierrez</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>

Carlos Gutierrez has been serving clients in San Diego County since 2005. Here’s what just a few of those clients have to say.

</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in San Diego, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>3 Tips for Investing in Real Estate</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/three-tips-for-investing-in-real-estate.html</link>
        
          <category>CA Real Estate</category>
        
        <author>Carlos Gutierrez</author>
        <pubDate>2017-07-07 14:15:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid>https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Carlos+Gutierrez/+Video/2017/June/San+Diego+Real+Estate+Agent-+Three+Tips+for+Investing+in+Real+Estate.mp4</guid>
        <description>

Today I wanted to share with you three tips for investing in rental properties.

You may have played the game of Monopoly and you know that the way to win that game is to have the most amount of properties and cash in the bank. Life can sometimes be a game as well, and we live in the perfect city for investing in rental properties. You might have thought about investing, and I wanted to share three things to consider before you invest.

“HAVE A ONE-YEAR PLAN AND FIVE-YEAR PLAN AND STICK TO THEM!”

1. Be selective when you buy. You need to make money when you buy the property. Often investors see a home at a low price and think they’ve found a good deal. However, you need to do your homework and research the area to determine whether it’s a good deal or not. Remember, price is what you pay, value is what you get.

2. Have an exit strategy. While investing in a rental property can be a great way to earn profit, don’t let it become such a large part of your portfolio that losing returns on it can ultimately bring you down with it. Have a one-year plan and then a five-year plan and stick to those plans.

3. Be ready for the unexpected! Things can quickly take an unexpected turn, and you need to be prepared for it. Houses can be a great investment, but are often full of unseen costs that correspond with those investments. So be prepared and able to address those issues when they present themselves.

If you have any questions about this or any other real estate topic, give me a call or shoot me an email. I’d be happy to help!
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Carlos+Gutierrez/+Video/2017/June/San+Diego+Real+Estate+Agent-+Three+Tips+for+Investing+in+Real+Estate.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Carlos+Gutierrez/+Video/2017/June/San+Diego+Real+Estate+Agent-+Three+Tips+for+Investing+in+Real+Estate.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>

Today I wanted to share with you three tips for investing in rental properties.

</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Carlos Gutierrez</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>

Today I wanted to share with you three tips for investing in rental properties.

</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in San Diego, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Why Is Summer a Great Time to List Your Home?</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/why-is-summer-great-time-to-list-your.html</link>
        
          <category>Home Seller Tips</category>
        
        <author>Carlos Gutierrez</author>
        <pubDate>2017-06-19 14:10:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid>https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Carlos+Gutierrez/+Video/2017/June/San+Diego+Real+Estate+Agent-+Why+Is+Summer+a+Great+Time+to+List+Your+Home%253F.mp4</guid>
        <description>

We all think of long, lazy days when we think of summer, but did you know that summer is actually a great time to sell your home?

Summertime is here; the days are longer, the weather is warmer, and everyone seems to be more relaxed. We all think of long, lazy days when we think of summer, but did you know it’s a great time to sell your home?

San Diego is in a pretty hot market right now. Home prices are up and mortgage rates continue to remain relatively low. We are at the top of this real estate market cycle, and there’s never been a better time to sell your property.

There are three main reasons why summer is a great time to sell your home:

1. Buyers are more relaxed. There aren’t any major holidays and school is out, so buyers are simply less stressed.

“BUYERS ARE MORE RELAXED DURING THE SUMMER.”

2. They have vacation homes on their mind. In San Diego, that means big business. People are looking for the perfect summer home or that income property. Income properties are a pretty hot commodity right now in our market.

3. Better weather means more traffic. When the weather is nice, you can expect 15% more traffic coming through your home. More traffic means more buyers.

If you’re interested in getting your home on the market this summer, just give me a call or send me an email. I would be happy to help you!
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Carlos+Gutierrez/+Video/2017/June/San+Diego+Real+Estate+Agent-+Why+Is+Summer+a+Great+Time+to+List+Your+Home%253F.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Carlos+Gutierrez/+Video/2017/June/San+Diego+Real+Estate+Agent-+Why+Is+Summer+a+Great+Time+to+List+Your+Home%253F.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>

We all think of long, lazy days when we think of summer, but did you know that summer is actually a great time to sell your home?

</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Carlos Gutierrez</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>

We all think of long, lazy days when we think of summer, but did you know that summer is actually a great time to sell your home?

</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in San Diego, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>How Can You Find Accurate Real Estate Info Online? </title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/how-can-you-find-accurate-real-estate.html</link>
        
          <category>San Diego Real Estate</category>
        
        <author>Carlos Gutierrez</author>
        <pubDate>2017-05-01 16:49:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid>https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Carlos+Gutierrez/+Video/2017/May/San+Diego+Real+Estate+Agent-+How+Can+You+Find+Accurate+Real+Estate+Info+Online%253F.mp4</guid>
        <description>

Homebuyers and sellers alike can get frustrated by the wealth of misinformation about real estate online. Today, I’ll give you a few tips to help you find accurate, updated real estate info.

The Internet is a great place to start your home search and find some information on what your home is worth. However, I hear from my friends and clients every day about how frustrating it is to sort out all of the information that they find online.

Popular sites like Zilow, Realtor.com, and Trulia can be great places to start out, but studies show that in cities like San Diego, the prices on those sites can be off by as much as 10% to 20%. In our market, that can mean a difference of anywhere from $50,000 to $200,000 off the actual market value of your home.

So, what can you do?

First off, don’t believe everything you read. If you are a buyer searching for homes, you can find some basic information online, but make sure that you go on multiple sites. Local sites like mine pull information directly from the MLS so you know that all the information you are looking at is up to date and accurate.

Buyers also need to get a pre-approval so that you can save time on your home search and know how much your loan limit is. In our market, having a pre-approval gives you negotiating power that will help you edge out the other buyers. Being pre-approved tells sellers that you are ready to buy.

“DON’T BELIEVE EVERYTHING YOU READ ON SITES LIKE ZILLOW OR TRULIA.”

You also need to stay calm. If you’re looking at homes on Zillow, don’t fall in love too fast. The prices may be wrong and, sometimes, the house may be listed as available even though it already sold months ago! An experienced agent like myself can guide you to the right homes.

If you are selling your home, you need accurate information to determine the value of your home. If your home is unique and you’ve made improvements, then you need a proper appraisal so that you get every dollar out of the sale of your home.

So, do your research. Check out multiple home value tools to get a range of what your home might be worth in the current market.

You should also check out the comps, or comparable properties. A real estate agent can do a comparable market analysis to see how your home stacks up against other similar, recently sold properties in your neighborhood. That is the most accurate way to determine what you can get for your home in this hot market.

Ultimately, you need to be careful when you are looking at homes online or if you are trying to find your home value with sites like Zillow or Trulia. If you have any other questions about finding accurate real estate information online, just give me a call or send me an email. I would be happy to help you!
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Carlos+Gutierrez/+Video/2017/May/San+Diego+Real+Estate+Agent-+How+Can+You+Find+Accurate+Real+Estate+Info+Online%253F.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Carlos+Gutierrez/+Video/2017/May/San+Diego+Real+Estate+Agent-+How+Can+You+Find+Accurate+Real+Estate+Info+Online%253F.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>

Homebuyers and sellers alike can get frustrated by the wealth of misinformation about real estate online. Today, I’ll give you a few tips to help you find accurate, updated real estate info.

</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Carlos Gutierrez</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>

Homebuyers and sellers alike can get frustrated by the wealth of misinformation about real estate online. Today, I’ll give you a few tips to help you find accurate, updated real estate info.

</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in San Diego, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>What Does the Slowing Market Mean for You?</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/what-does-slowing-market-mean-for-you.html</link>
        
          <category>Market Update</category>
        
        <author>Carlos Gutierrez</author>
        <pubDate>2017-04-17 11:05:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid>https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Carlos+Gutierrez/+Video/2017/April/San+Diego+Real+Estate+Agent-+What+Does+the+Slowing+Market+Mean+for+You%253F.mp4</guid>
        <description>

Home prices are slowing down for the second month in a row.
What does the future hold for home prices in the San Diego market?

San Diego is slowing down for the second month in a row. What does that mean for you? Although the news has to be shocking these days to capture the public’s attention, I’m here to give you just the facts and only the facts about what is really happening in the real estate market.

The latest numbers show that San Diego County home prices rose 5.7% this year, just below the national average of 5.9%, but not by much. We are slowing down, however. This time last year, home prices were increasing at a 7% higher rate than the national average.

“THE MARKET IS STRONG FOR THE TIME BEING.”

According to the experts, higher home prices and increasing mortgage rates will shrink the number of households that can actually afford to buy a home and force prices to decline.

The great news for you is we aren’t there quite yet, and the market is holding strong for the time being. If you have equity in your home, it’s a great time to think about selling. If you’re not sure what your home is actually worth, I can show you an accurate home valuation right here on my page.

If you have any other real estate questions or if you’re looking to buy or sell in San Diego, give me a call or send me an email today. I look forward to hearing from you soon.
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Carlos+Gutierrez/+Video/2017/April/San+Diego+Real+Estate+Agent-+What+Does+the+Slowing+Market+Mean+for+You%253F.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Carlos+Gutierrez/+Video/2017/April/San+Diego+Real+Estate+Agent-+What+Does+the+Slowing+Market+Mean+for+You%253F.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>

Home prices are slowing down for the second month in a row.
What does the future hold for home prices in the San Diego market?

</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Carlos Gutierrez</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>

Home prices are slowing down for the second month in a row.
What does the future hold for home prices in the San Diego market?

</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in San Diego, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>How to Make Sure Your Family Is Protected</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/how-to-make-sure-your-family-is.html</link>
        
          <category>Real Estate Investment</category>
        
        <author>Carlos Gutierrez</author>
        <pubDate>2017-02-27 11:23:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <guid>https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Carlos+Gutierrez/+Video/2017/February/San+Diego+Real+Estate+Agent-+How+to+Make+Sure+Your+Family+Is+Protected.mp4</guid>
        <description>

Dealing with the loss of a family member can be especially difficult when the necessary planning was not done ahead of time. There are three steps you can take now to protect your family.

There is nothing more devastating than dealing with the loss or illness of a family member. That difficult time can turn into a nightmare if you haven’t taken care of the necessary planning ahead of time.

I was recently working with a family who had just lost their mother and, when selling her estate, they realized there was no will or trust in place. Now they have to deal with the challenges of probate, which costs a lot of time and money.

There are three things you can do now to make sure that your loved ones are protected after you’re gone:

1. Talk about it now. Don’t wait until there is a tragedy or illness to have the difficult conversations with your family. Be open and honest about what you want to happen to your home and your investments.

“BE OPEN AND HONEST ABOUT WHAT YOU WANT TO HAPPEN TO YOUR HOME AND INVESTMENTS.”

2. Put it in writing. Make sure that you have a will or trust. It’s smart to put your wishes in writing so that your children and other beneficiaries are not left trying to sort out everything while they are in mourning. Not having a will can complicate relationships and cost your loved ones thousands of dollars in attorney’s fees. Have a frank and open discussion about your estate plans with the people who you love, who should be in the know.

3. Consult a real estate professional to ensure that your plans and assets are protected. A real estate agent can help you determine whether a revocable or irrevocable trust would be best.

This can be a very difficult topic to navigate, but it is important to take these three steps in order to protect your family. If you have any other questions or need further guidance on this topic, please don’t hesitate to give me a call. I am here to help you.
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Carlos+Gutierrez/+Video/2017/February/San+Diego+Real+Estate+Agent-+How+to+Make+Sure+Your+Family+Is+Protected.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Carlos+Gutierrez/+Video/2017/February/San+Diego+Real+Estate+Agent-+How+to+Make+Sure+Your+Family+Is+Protected.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>

Dealing with the loss of a family member can be especially difficult when the necessary planning was not done ahead of time. There are three steps you can take now to protect your family.

</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Carlos Gutierrez</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>

Dealing with the loss of a family member can be especially difficult when the necessary planning was not done ahead of time. There are three steps you can take now to protect your family.

</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in San Diego, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>How to Make Your Neighborhood Cleanup a Success</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/how-to-make-your-neighborhood-cleanup.html</link>
        
          <category>Community Help</category>
        
        <author>Carlos Gutierrez</author>
        <pubDate>2017-01-30 13:47:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <guid>https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Carlos+Gutierrez/+Video/2017/January/San+Diego+Real+Estate+Agent-+How+to+Make+Your+Neighborhood+Cleanup+a+Success.mp4</guid>
        <description>

There are a ton of positive benefits to organizing a community cleanup project. Here are a few of them.

Your cleanup day is almost here! You need help, so I’ve got some great tips to share. I really enjoy helping others write their real estate success stories. As promised, I am here to give you some tips on how to organize and motivate the people in your neighborhood for your own community beautification project. Here are three things to keep in mind when planning your cleanup:

1. Show me the money. You don’t have to pay people in cash, you just need to share with them how much value will be added to their home by cleaning up the neighborhood. The nicer it looks, the more home values go up.

“THE WORLD IS IN NEED OF POSITIVE COMMUNITY STORIES.”

2. Shout it out. Post on local neighborhood Facebook groups or even on Craigslist to increase turnout. Make a flyer, walk the neighborhood, and introduce yourself to some neighbors you haven’t met before. Let them know when and where the dumpsters will be located. You can also contact your local media to let them know and ask if they could get the word out. The world is in so much need right now of positive community stories. The local media loves those stories and are happy to share them. Start making your own positive news story today.

3. Be positive. Your energy will spark others to want to take action. Maintaining a positive attitude is one of the keys to ensuring success.

If you have any questions for me, don’t hesitate to give me a call or send me an email. I look forward to hearing from you soon.
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Carlos+Gutierrez/+Video/2017/January/San+Diego+Real+Estate+Agent-+How+to+Make+Your+Neighborhood+Cleanup+a+Success.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Carlos+Gutierrez/+Video/2017/January/San+Diego+Real+Estate+Agent-+How+to+Make+Your+Neighborhood+Cleanup+a+Success.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>

There are a ton of positive benefits to organizing a community cleanup project. Here are a few of them.

</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Carlos Gutierrez</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>

There are a ton of positive benefits to organizing a community cleanup project. Here are a few of them.

</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in San Diego, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>3 Tips to Find Resources for Community Beautification</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/3-tips-to-kick-off-your-community.html</link>
        
          <category>Community Help</category>
        
        <author>Carlos Gutierrez</author>
        <pubDate>2017-01-13 17:30:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <guid>https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Carlos+Gutierrez/Video/San+Diego+Real+Estate+Agent-+3+Tips+to+Kick+Off+Your+Community+Beautification+Project.mp4</guid>
        <description>

Today, I have three tips to get you the resources you need for your community beautification project.

You decided to beautify your community—congratulations! You have the drive and the goals, but you don’t have any of the resources yet. Here are three great tips to help you get started:

1. Reach out to local waste management companies and ask them to donate a dumpster for the day. Many waste management companies will donate dumpsters during the weekend for all of the neighborhood’s trash.

2. Contact local business owners and ask if they are willing to help sponsor the event. Maybe they can throw in some money, food, flowers, or rocks in exchange for advertising and posting on social media. Let them know that you will pass out flyers and post on social media to spotlight their company as they help the community clean up.

“YOU CAN FIND FREE SUPPLIES ON CRAIGSLIST.”

3. Search Craigslist for free items like dirt, rocks, or plants. A lot of people have things that they just want hauled away. If you have a truck, then you have access to some free resources.

Community beautification projects help increase home values in your neighborhood and lower the crime rate. Next, we’ll talk about how to organize and motivate others.

In the meantime, if you have any questions, just give me a call or send me an email. I would be happy to help you!
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Carlos+Gutierrez/Video/San+Diego+Real+Estate+Agent-+3+Tips+to+Kick+Off+Your+Community+Beautification+Project.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Carlos+Gutierrez/Video/San+Diego+Real+Estate+Agent-+3+Tips+to+Kick+Off+Your+Community+Beautification+Project.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>

Today, I have three tips to get you the resources you need for your community beautification project.

</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Carlos Gutierrez</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>

Today, I have three tips to get you the resources you need for your community beautification project.

</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in San Diego, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>A very important message from Carlos, Bella & Jeannete Gutierrez</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/happy-holidays-from-carlos-gutierrez.html</link>
        
          <category>Happy Holidays</category>
        
        <author>Carlos Gutierrez</author>
        <pubDate>2016-12-19 15:16:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <guid>https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Carlos+Gutierrez/Carlos-Gutierrez-Dec-2016-1-YouTube.jpg</guid>
        <description>

The holiday season is finally here. We wanted to take a moment to wish you and your family the best. We are grateful to have you in our lives, especially this time of year.

Happy holidays everyone! I am here today with my daughter, Bella, and my wife, Jeanette. We wanted to take this time to wish you all a happy, healthy, and prosperous holiday. From our family to yours, we wanted to wish you the best this season.

“HAVE FUN SPENDING TIME WITH YOUR LOVED ONES THIS HOLIDAY SEASON.”

We are very lucky to have you in our lives, so we also want to say thank you. We appreciate you. Our mantra in 2017 is the attitude of gratitude. We are so thankful for so much and we hope that you take some time this holiday season to think about what you are thankful for too. It’s a great exercise, and it really puts things into perspective.

Have fun spending time with your friends, family, and coworkers this holiday season and know that we are grateful for all of you. Happy holidays, Feliz Navidad, and merry Christmas. We look forward to seeing you in 2017.
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Carlos+Gutierrez/Carlos-Gutierrez-Dec-2016-1-YouTube.jpg" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Carlos+Gutierrez/Carlos-Gutierrez-Dec-2016-1-YouTube.jpg" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>

The holiday season is finally here. We wanted to take a moment to wish you and your family the best. We are grateful to have you in our lives, especially this time of year.

</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Carlos Gutierrez</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>

The holiday season is finally here. We wanted to take a moment to wish you and your family the best. We are grateful to have you in our lives, especially this time of year.

</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in San Diego, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Why I Always Put Community Before Self</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/why-i-always-put-community-before-self.html</link>
        
          <category>Community Help</category>
        
        <author>Carlos Gutierrez</author>
        <pubDate>2016-11-28 14:24:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <guid>https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Carlos+Gutierrez/Video/San+Diego+Real+Estate+Agent-+Higher+Home+Values%252C+Lower+Crime+-+It%2527s+Easier+Than+You+Think+(1).mp4</guid>
        <description>

I love helping people write their own real estate success stories and I’m passionate about giving back to the community here in San Diego. As I learned from my mentors, putting your community before yourself is key.

Recently, I helped beautify a San Diego neighborhood out in Grant Hill. Check out the video above and you’ll see a clip from NBC7 about our latest clean up effort. I got permission from the city to clean up the area, so I donated $10,000 to the project, got some volunteers together, and we got to work.

You have to be the change that you want to see in the world. Watch for my next videos that show how you can start a community clean up in your own neighborhood. Getting organized to help your community does not cost as much as you think.

Remember, if you put time and energy into helping your community, people will see that you care. If you have any questions in the meantime, just give me a call or send me an email. I would be happy to help you!
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Carlos+Gutierrez/Video/San+Diego+Real+Estate+Agent-+Higher+Home+Values%252C+Lower+Crime+-+It%2527s+Easier+Than+You+Think+(1).mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Carlos+Gutierrez/Video/San+Diego+Real+Estate+Agent-+Higher+Home+Values%252C+Lower+Crime+-+It%2527s+Easier+Than+You+Think+(1).mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>

I love helping people write their own real estate success stories and I’m passionate about giving back to the community here in San Diego. As I learned from my mentors, putting your community before yourself is key.

</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Carlos Gutierrez</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>

I love helping people write their own real estate success stories and I’m passionate about giving back to the community here in San Diego. As I learned from my mentors, putting your community before yourself is key.

</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in San Diego, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>How You Can Increase Your Home's Value</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/be-change-you-want-to-see-in-world.html</link>
        
          <category>CA Real Estate</category>
        
        <author>Carlos Gutierrez</author>
        <pubDate>2016-11-10 14:53:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <guid>https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Carlos+Gutierrez/San+Diego+Real+Estate+Agent-+Making+One+Neighborhood+to+Outshine+Them+All.mp4</guid>
        <description>

So you want to be the change in your neighborhood, but you don’t know where to start. It’s okay—I know the feeling, and I’m here to help. In my last video, I gave you some tips on how to organize your own community beautification project. Today, I want to share with you three great tips on how to continue this community outreach:

1. Contact your local city council member or local area representative. These people are committed to helping improve neighborhoods. Set up a time to sit down and talk with them or just call them and parlay over the phone.

2. Create a list of specific goals you hope to achieve. This project can become overwhelming if you don’t break it down into smaller, more manageable tasks. For example, you might just write down “clear all trash off west side of Main Street.” Make it that specific so you have an attainable goal to share with the rest of the team.

3. Get out there and talk to your neighbors. Start knocking on doors and letting people know what’s happening. If you don’t know your neighbors, introduce yourself. If you really want to start beautifying a neighborhood, you want support in numbers.

“Beautifying a neighborhood is an initiative everyone can get behind.”

Everyone wins when you clean up a neighborhood. Not only is it nice to see a clean, well-maintained area, but home values will go up, crime will go down, and it’s something everyone can get behind.

In my next video, we’ll talk about how you can get the materials to get this job done. In the meantime, if you have any questions about the community beautification process or anything real estate-related, please don’t hesitate to give me a call or shoot me an email. I’d be happy to help you!
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Carlos+Gutierrez/San+Diego+Real+Estate+Agent-+Making+One+Neighborhood+to+Outshine+Them+All.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Carlos+Gutierrez/San+Diego+Real+Estate+Agent-+Making+One+Neighborhood+to+Outshine+Them+All.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>

So you want to be the change in your neighborhood, but you don’t know where to start. It’s okay—I know the feeling, and I’m here to help. In my last video, I gave you some tips on how to organize your own community beautification project. Today, I want to share with you three great tips on how to continue this community outreach:

</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Carlos Gutierrez</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>

So you want to be the change in your neighborhood, but you don’t know where to start. It’s okay—I know the feeling, and I’m here to help. In my last video, I gave you some tips on how to organize your own community beautification project. Today, I want to share with you three great tips on how to continue this community outreach:

</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in San Diego, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>3 Ways to Find the Right Realtor for You</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/3-ways-to-find-right-realtor-for-you.html</link>
        
          <category>CA Real Estate</category>
        
        <author>Carlos Gutierrez</author>
        <pubDate>2016-09-09 11:06:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid>https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Carlos+Gutierrez/San+Diego+Real+Estate+Agent+-+3+Ways+to+Find+the+Right+Realtor+For+You.mp4</guid>
        <description>

Have you ever met a bad Realtor? They can change the way you view this profession.

When you need a real estate professional, it can be hard to find someone you can trust. When the market is hot like it’s been lately, a lot of people think they can make a quick buck selling real estate, and these people can be hard to spot. To help you differentiate between a good Realtor and a bad one, I want to share the three things you should ask a Realtor before you decide to work with them.

“Is real estate a hobby or a profession for them?”

1. How long have you been selling real estate full-time, and how many homes are you selling? This will show you if real estate is a profession for them or just a hobby. People who think they can use real estate to make a quick buck don’t last long in this market.

2. How do you determine the price of a property? Listing your home at the right price can be the difference between selling or lingering on the market with no offers. Pricing a home is more than checking the comps—a true professional will have a comprehensive strategy for pricing.

3. What is your marketing plan? Sticking a sign in the yard and listing your house on the MLS is not a marketing plan. There are more than 30 different ways a professional agent can market your home, so make sure your agent is maximizing their network and has a strategy to help you achieve your real estate goals.

I really hope these tips help you find the right Realtor when the time comes. If you have any more questions about finding the right agent, please feel free to give me a call or send me an email. I hope to hear from you soon!
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Carlos+Gutierrez/San+Diego+Real+Estate+Agent+-+3+Ways+to+Find+the+Right+Realtor+For+You.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Carlos+Gutierrez/San+Diego+Real+Estate+Agent+-+3+Ways+to+Find+the+Right+Realtor+For+You.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>

Have you ever met a bad Realtor? They can change the way you view this profession.

</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Carlos Gutierrez</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>

Have you ever met a bad Realtor? They can change the way you view this profession.

</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in San Diego, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>How Can You Avoid Overpricing Your Home?</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/how-can-you-avoid-overpricing-your-home.html</link>
        
          <category>Real Estate</category>
        
        <author>Carlos Gutierrez</author>
        <pubDate>2016-07-12 12:59:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid>https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Carlos+Gutierrez/San+Diego+Real+Estate+Agent+-+How+Can+You+Avoid+Overpricing+Your+Home.mp4</guid>
        <description>

When the market is hot and agents are fighting over listings, it’s easy to get caught up in the crossfire, which can cost you the sale of the home. One of the worst things that I see agents do all too often is overprice homes. Lucky for you, I have three easy ways to ensure this doesn’t happen to you.

1. Use a trusted home valuation tool. Don’t rely on sites like Zillow and Trulia. Their home values can be off by as much as 25%!

2. Get a professional opinion. Once you get an online valuation, call a professional to come see your home. Each home is unique, and there are many factors that can make your home worth more than your neighbors’. I love to give homeowners this information because it empowers them to make the best decisions.

3. Keep current. Home values in markets like San Diego can change quickly and your information can become outdated pretty quick. Don’t hesitate to subscribe to monthly emails or newsletters to stay in the loop.

“Home values change all the time in San Diego, so it’s important to stay updated.”

If you have any questions about how I can help and empower you in your real estate journey, please don’t hesitate to reach out to us. We would love to hear from you!
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Carlos+Gutierrez/San+Diego+Real+Estate+Agent+-+How+Can+You+Avoid+Overpricing+Your+Home.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Carlos+Gutierrez/San+Diego+Real+Estate+Agent+-+How+Can+You+Avoid+Overpricing+Your+Home.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>

When the market is hot and agents are fighting over listings, it’s easy to get caught up in the crossfire, which can cost you the sale of the home. One of the worst things that I see agents do all too often is overprice homes. Lucky for you, I have three easy ways to ensure this doesn’t happen to you.

</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Carlos Gutierrez</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>

When the market is hot and agents are fighting over listings, it’s easy to get caught up in the crossfire, which can cost you the sale of the home. One of the worst things that I see agents do all too often is overprice homes. Lucky for you, I have three easy ways to ensure this doesn’t happen to you.

</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in San Diego, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
    <copyright>Carlos Gutierrez</copyright>
    <media:credit role="author">Carlos Gutierrez</media:credit>
    <media:rating>nonadult</media:rating>
    <media:description type="plain">If you are looking to buy or sell a home, get all the information and the latest updates, tips, and tricks from Coldwell Banker - your professional San Diego Real Estate Agents.</media:description>
  </channel>
</rss>
